comluv.com 2009-11-26

# Privacy | Comment Luv

## Privacy

## ComLuv Privacy Statement

### Introduction

ComLuv.com is dedicated to protecting the privacy of our users by taking all possible measures to protect their personally identifiable information. This privacy statement outlines these measures and discloses the privacy practices of ComLuv.com

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our user information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected online and offline.

In offline situation user information is access is restricted to computers in my office only. The servers that I store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure data center environment.

### Information Collection and Use

ComLuv.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. I will not release any personably identifying information unless you specifically authorize me to do so or unless required by the appropriate law enforcement officials.

### Registration

In order to use the services here, a user must first complete the sign-up form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on this site for which they have expressed interest. Demographic information collected is used for my own analysis purposes to improve the services offered.

### Log Files

I use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information

### Sharing Demographic Information

I will share aggregated demographic information with partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

### Customer Communications

The site will send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and email address. Established Members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter via email or letter mail as part of my customer communications which can be unsubscribed to at any time. In addition, I also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from important customer communications sent via the site dashboard, which contain information about any changes to the service or terms that could affect your use of the site. 

### Search Every CommentLuv Enabled Blog  
(active in the past 7 days)
